<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Becky Sweger</title>
    <link>https://www.beckysweger.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Becky Sweger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 09:09:54 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.beckysweger.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tech Hiring: The Streetlight Effect</title>
      <link>https://www.beckysweger.com/writing/tech-streetlight-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 09:09:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.beckysweger.com/writing/tech-streetlight-effect/</guid>
      <description>We look for engineers where the light is shining</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://www.beckysweger.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 17:03:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.beckysweger.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a technical leader and software engineer who specializes in designing, building, and shipping data-centric applications.
Currently a Principal Data Engineer at Trello (Atlassian), I previously held an appointment at 18F, a government-embedded startup created under the Obama administration. There, I led the technical implementation of the United States&#39; first open data law.
A twenty-five year tech veteran, I&amp;rsquo;ve held leadership positions in higher education, healthcare, and the non-profit sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects and Talks</title>
      <link>https://www.beckysweger.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 16:44:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.beckysweger.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Selected Talks  StrangeLoop - Software With a Mission, 2018: From Coder to Bureaucrat (co-presenter) FiveCollege Stats and Data Science Research Bytes: Columnar Data Storage and the Separation of Compute and Storage, 2018 Western MA Full Stack Meetup: The Humble Dataframe DATA Act Summit, 2017: Leveraging Technology to Modernize Government (panel) DATA Act Training, 2017: Why the DATA Act Matters: New Uses for Standardized Spending Information 18F: Data Munging With Python and Pandas New England Regional Developers (NERD) Summit: Intro to IPython Notebooks Association of Public Data Users (APDU): Transitioning to Open Government Data Wharton School of Business: Elegant and Efficient Database Design  Selected Projects DATA Act: USAspending API Led the buildout of an API that presents, for the first time, a unified view of U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
