<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>beckysweger.com</title>
    <link>https://www.beckysweger.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on beckysweger.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 22:27:06 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.beckysweger.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.beckysweger.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 17:03:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.beckysweger.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a tech leader and software engineer who specializes in designing, munging, and shipping data.
Currently I&amp;rsquo;m a principal data engineer for Trello at Atlassian. Previously, I was a U.S. federal civil servant, serving as a tech lead and member of the engineering team at 18F, a consultancy inside the General Services Administration.
During my 18F tenure, I lead the technical implementation of the DATA Act, the nation’s first open data law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.beckysweger.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 16:44:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.beckysweger.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Talks  2018 StrangeLoop Software With a Mission: From Coder to Bureaucrat (co-presenter) 2018 FiveCollege Stats and Data Science Research Bytes: Columnar Data Storage and the Separation of Compute and Storage 2018 Western MA Full Stack Meetup: The Humble Dataframe 2017 DATA Act Summit: Leveraging Technology to Modernize Government (panel) 2017 DATA Act Training: Why the DATA Act Matters: New Uses for Standardized Spending Information 18F Tech Talk: Data Munging With Python and Pandas 2014 NERD Summit: Intro to IPython Notebooks 2012 Association of Public Data Users: Transitioning to Open Government Data Wharton Computing Tech Talk: Elegant and Efficient Database Design  DATA Act: USAspending API Led the buildout of an API that presents, for the first time, a unified view of U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>